[Music]
hello everyone
today i wanted to share a little bit
about how i
imbue a sense of whimsy for lack of a
better word
into many aspects of my home and life
as you can see my cottage is alternative
in its style
and i would say rather unusual in
comparison to more mainstream home decor
however to strictly speak on the
practicalities of transforming this room
i think
would miss a lot of my philosophy behind
creating a space in which you feel
welcomed and accepted
no matter who you are
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
do
to explain my philosophy i must begin by
asking you a question
have you ever listened to a beautiful
song that has touched your soul so
deeply
that it almost hurts when it's over
maybe you've experienced this
when you've watched an incredibly
poignant scene in your favorite movie
read an atmospheric book that
transported you to another world
or maybe simply the feeling of being
utterly and completely
enraptured by the beauty of whatever it
is you have just
experienced
i think as children it happens more
often since we're still new to the world
and all its fascinating elements
i remember seeing a butterfly wing under
a microscope for the first time when i
was
and gasped at the stunning intricacy and
other worldliness of the design
since then i've loved butterflies and
you can always spot some in my room
as we become adults it can be easy to go
in and day out without having moments
like these
i have again discovered a love of daily
life through reclaiming the curiosity
and daydreaming of my youth
and this has impacted how i decorate and
the crafts that i make
[Music]
okay
hmm
[Music]
i know not everyone cares to recreate a
sense of wonder and surrealism within
their living space
also maybe you can't relate to this at
all and i'm sounding a little odd right
now
it is okay i'm used to it
anyway i would love to know your
thoughts my reason for speaking on this
is because i've designed my space in a
way to remind me of those precious and
beautiful whimsical moments
i wish i could hang on to forever i love
adding little details and cutouts
my favorite books painting the walls
making things by hand
i'm well aware i cannot live in a
fantasy world and i wouldn't wish to
however having a dreamy space that makes
me feel calm
creative and imaginative gives me
strength to deal with the world
on days when things seem overly negative
or scary
[Music]
you can see this philosophy directly
impacting these videos
they are creative outlets an artistic
take on home life that sees things as i
said once before
not as they are all the time but maybe
how they could be
i love to emphasize the beauty of plants
art and sunlight through these videos
but i'm not able to stay in the present
all the time and enjoy these things to
the fullest
that is why i love to make these videos
and re-center through the process
it forces me to slow down and remember
what's important
life can be beautiful and meaningful not
only through its achievements but in its
simplest
moments
[Music]
let me know your perspectives on home
life and how you create a space that
gives you comfort
because i think that's what many of us
are looking for a haven that draws us in
and gives us a sense of safety i feel
embraced
by my home because i've put so much time
into it
so many handmade items and details if
i'm ever overwhelmed or filled with
worry i like to walk into this room and
take a deep breath
and remind myself that i am safe
sending you hugs wherever you are
[Music]
you